artofzoo.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy – ArtOfZoo – Official Site

ArtOfZoo.com has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our commitment to personal privacy. The following policy document discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for websites owned and operated by us.

Generally speaking, when you arrive at or leave our websites, our servers automatically receive information including but not limited to:

– your internet protocol (IP) address  
– the IP address of the site you came from  
– the IP address of the site you went to following our websites  
– the type of browser you use  
– pages visited whilst on our websites

We use this information in order to improve our service and the experience of using our websites. We may also use IP address information to control aspects of website access, to identify and gather non-personal demographic information, and to optimise the performance of our hardware.

In addition to the above information, we may use cookies. Cookies are widely used, and are tiny text files that are downloaded to your computer in order for our websites to recognise you as a previous visitor, subscriber or member. Cookies contain no sensitive information.

Account signup, subscription and purchase web forms on our websites collect various information including but not limited to:

– contact information  
– financial information  
– product purchase information

This information is only collected upon submission by you.

Contact information is primarily used to communicate with members and customers as necessary regarding any membership, product or billing-related topics.

From time to time, contact information may be used to transmit promotional and marketing information from us. We do not sell or rent your information to third party companies. All marketing communications from us carry the facility to unsubscribe from further such communications in the future as per international spam / unsolicited email conventions.

Financial information that is transmitted to us by users is collected and used for the purpose of processing a billing transaction based upon the users purchase requests for products / services.

Personal information will only be disclosed in situations where it is appropriate to cooperate in investigations of fraud or other illegal activity. Furthermore, we will disclose information in response to a subpoena, warrant, court order, levy, attachment, order of a court-appointed receiver or other comparable legal process, including subpoenas from private parties in a civil action.

Your personal information will be stored and processed on our servers in Denmark, Spain and Russia. ArtOfZoo.com will hold and transmit your personal information in a safe, confidential and secure environment. If you object to your personal information being transferred or used as described in this Privacy Policy, please do not create an account, make purchases from, or use this website or any affiliated website in any way.
